like you
how this offense may go.
Could be good for you as a running back.
What about What about this offense you
think kind of appeals to you as a
running back? Uh the way you guys run
the ball,
the way the way quarterback moves in the
in the pocket.
Just
all of it.
Um
and and just
how would you I guess sort of describe
your game? What are the assets of the
specific specific typically see out of a
backfield where you think you can
contribute? Uh my speed, being able to
catch the ball in the backfield and pass
protection.
Thank you.
Anybody else?
Can I ask one more? Yep.
Hey Jerome, what is it that you maybe
you felt like you learned most in your
first couple years in Cleveland that you
can apply here?
Um I was able to sit behind Chubb and
Kareem, so I actually learned a lot. Um
sitting behind Chubb
uh
helped me, you know, pace out the NFL,
how to work, when to work, and and
pretty much how I am now. Uh
real quiet, just come in and do my
business and
you know, be a great teammate and go
home.
Cool.
All right, thanks Jerome. Appreciate it.
>> Thank you.